<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers on Aviv Segall</title>
    <link>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papers on Aviv Segall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://segaviv.github.io/papers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital 3D Smocking Design</title>
      <link>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper4/</guid>
      <description>The paper presents a method for digitally previewing a smocking pattern design by formulating smocking as a graph embedding and shape deformation problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterative closest conformal maps between planar domains</title>
      <link>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper3/</guid>
      <description>The paper introduces an alternating minimization algorithm utilizing the Cauchy-Green complex coordinates to efficiently compute a conformal map between planar domains with initial global alignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hele-shaw flow simulation with interactive control using complex barycentric coordinates</title>
      <link>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper2/</guid>
      <description>The paper explores Hele-Shaw flow, a slow viscous liquid flow between parallel plates, proposing an efficient simulation method using a complex-variable formulation of generalized barycentric coordinates, enabling interactive user control and extending applicability to the exterior domain for simulating two-phase flow and diverse patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line accessibility of free form surfaces</title>
      <link>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://segaviv.github.io/papers/paper1/</guid>
      <description>The paper presents an algoirthm for computing the visual hull of a parameteric surface in an arrangement of additional occluding surfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
